right say welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep 10 and God spake all
these words saying I am the Lord thy God
which have brought thee out of the land
of Egypt out of the house of bondage
thou shall have no other gods before me
thou should not make unto thee any
Graven image or any likeness of anything
that is in heaven the b or that is in
the earth beneath or that is in a water
under the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for why
the Lord thy God am a jealous God
visiting the iniquities of the fathers
upon the children into the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me
and showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that take of his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall thou lay and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God and thou
shall not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man's servant nor
thy made servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in the m and rested
the seventh day wherefore the Lord bless
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee thou shall not kill
thou shall not commit adultery thou sh
not steal thou sh not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou shall not
cover thy neighbor's house thou sh not
cover thy neighbor's wife nor his man's
servant nor his maid servant nor his Ox
nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors we read Exodus 21-17 and may
the Lord have a blessing to the reading
of his words in Jesus name we pray
amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
the questions that we will not answer
are the vague and the long scripture
questions as well as questions of debate
we are not here to debate but we are
here to spread the true Gospel of Jesus
so please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program also this is a live stream so
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life we just ask
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture maximum let me introduce to
you the family that's on the panel this
evening our brother Jerome rest in peace
Brother Dre good evening brother Julius
good evening everybody brother tanzel
good evening sister Deborah good
evening and we have Casey as well as the
guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell sister Deborah what is our first
question of the
evening all right uh there are several
held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so Deborah Davis asks
since everything is an example for us
when we go to the place of safety or
when Jesus returns will everyone 20 and
under be allowed into the place of
safety and receive Jesus
Mark all right we're going to ask the
guest caller can you share some light on
that question
sure first thing is it wasn't the case
where 20 years old was kept out of the
place of safety all Israel went into the
Wilderness and all
Israel were going to the Wilderness in
the last days thing about it is uh uh
they all everybody came out of Egypt but
everybody didn't get out of uh uh get
out of the
wildness now let's go in the uh
except for the people that was uh 20
years and under 19 years and under let's
go into uh numbers the 14th chapter and
look at this numbers 14 and we're going
to read from 28 to 32 verse
28-32 read it when you get there say
unto them as truly as I live sayeth the
Lord as he have spoken in my ear so will
I do to you your carcass is shall fall
in this Wilderness and all that were
numbered of you according to your whole
number from 20 years old and upward
which have murmured against
me doubtless ye have not come into the
land concerning that which I swear to
make you dwell therein save Kayla the
son of jeffi and Joshua the son of nun
but your little ones which he said
should be a prey them will I bring in
and they shall know the land which ye
have despised but as for you your
carcasses they shall fall in this
Wilderness now right there everybody
went into the Wilderness but everybody
didn't get out of the
Wilderness from 20 years from 19 uh uh
20 years and up except for Joshua and
Caleb they the only one that came that
got into the promised land that was 20
years you know that that was uh uh uh
grown when they came out of Egypt now
the same thing you can get in the
wilderness go to the Wilderness but will
you be able to get out of it it ain't
nothing is different let's go into
Ezekiel the 20th
chapter and we're going to read from
verse 33 to
38 as I live said the Lord
but we at 10 Z you mind repeating it
Ezekiel 20 vers 33-
38 as I live sayth the Lord God surely
with a mighty hand and with a stretch
out arm and with Fury poured out will I
rule over you and I will bring you out
from the people and will gather you out
of the countries wherein you are
scattered with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury pour out
and I will bring you into the Wilderness
of the people and there will I plead
with you face to face like I pleaded
with your fathers and the Wilderness of
the land of Egypt so would I plead but
you say the Lord God and I will cause
you to pass under the rod and I will
bring you into the bond of the Covenant
and I will Purge out from among you the
rebels and them that transgress against
me and I will bring them forth out of
the country where they sourn and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel
and ye shall know that I am the
Lord there not going to be anything
different just like it was everybody
went into the Wilderness but everybody
didn't come out same thing here that
Persian was when he killed everybody
from 20 years and up except for josua
and this
time anybody that don't want that don't
want to come under the
Covenant so say and that mean that they
going to die in the wilderness so it's
not a thing of getting in the wilderness
you going to get in
there thing is will you get out that's
all I have to say will you get out all
right thank you for that hope that
answer that question as we move on to
our next one moving on barar steel says
why do we dispute what the Bible says
when it says the Angels defiled
themselves and took themselves women
why would it say it if it's not true and
Job 1 verse 6 and Job 38 verse 7 is
given all right brother Dre that
question is in need of some light what
you say let's go to those scriptures you
provided and see if it says what you are
saying that we're disputing let's go to
job 1 and six read that when you get it
tanel
Job 1 and6 yes now there was a day when
the sons of God came to present
themselves before the Lord and Satan
came also among them sister that didn't
say anything about
angels defiling themselves with women
are sleeping with women said nothing
about it in that verse now let's go to
Job 38 and7 the other verse that you
provided let's go there and read that
when you get it trans read
it when the morning star sang together
and all the sons of God shouted for
Joy now sister again that said nothing
about what you are saying we are
disputing okay said nothing about it but
let's go to something Jesus said let's
go to Matthew the 22nd chapter and take
a look at that Matthew
22 and we gonna read verse 30
Matthew 22
and3 Matthew 22 and3 yes sir go ahead
for in the resurrection they neither
marry nor are given in marriage but are
as the angels of God in heaven so this
question was asked after this son died
and his brothers raised up seed and
there was seven of them and they said
well who's wife is this woman going to
be in the resurrection since seven of
them had her right read verse 30 one
more time pay attention to this sister
go ahead for in the resurrection they
neither marry nor are given in marriage
but are as the angels of God in heaven
the Angels do not marry either sister
nor are they given in marriage right so
that is a falsehood that is taught out
of the Book of Enoch that tells you
about angels sleeping with women having
450 fet babies my question is is is if
that is the case where are they
now that's all I
got let me throw something man see they
come up with this this son of God
because of what it says when Jesus got
baptized and started running this
lineage and somebody let's go and see if
we can run that lineage
let's go that's Luke
3 huh that's Luke 3 starting at
23 Luke 3 and
23 okay uh uh Luke three and let's see
how we going started uh let me
see Luke 3 and 23 okay go
ahead and Jesus himself began to be
about 30 years of age being as was
supposed the son of Joseph which was the
son of
heli which was the son of Mai which was
the son of Levi which was the son of
melchi which was the son of Jana which
was the son of
Joseph which was the son of Maas which
was the son of Amos which was the son of
naon which was the son of el Eli which
was the son of Nag
skip down do all that reading okay skip
down to verse uh uh uh let's pick it up
what the people we know about
uh
34 start at 34 and go
ahead which was the son of Jacob which
was the son of Isaac which was the son
of Abraham which was the son of thra
which was the son of n which was the son
of s Sarat which was the son of Ragu
which was the son of Fel which was the
son of Heber which was the son of
Salah which was the son of Canan which
was the son of arax which was the son of
s which was the son of no which was the
son of lamech which was the son of
Methuselah which was the son of Enoch
which was the son of Jared which was the
son of me melel which was the son of
Canaan which was the son of Enos which
was the son of Seth which was the son of
Adam which was the son Son of
God that's what it was now these are all
the sons the lineage that come from Adam
and didn't turn away from the Lord see
Cain is the one that sinned against God
when he made when hehh murdered his
brother now let's go into uh uh
uh let's go into Genesis the 5th
chapter because he went on back into
Adam which was the son of God these are
the people that followed God and didn't
turn away but it was different with Cain
was disinherited so now uh Exodus 5 and
start reading at verse one I'm sorry uh
uh Genesis 5 genesis 5 and
one this is the book of the generations
of Adam and the day that God created man
in the likeness of God made he him male
and female created he them and bless
them and called their name Adam in the
day they were
created uhhuh and Adam lived 130 years
and beg a son in his own likeness after
his image and called his name
Seth wait a minute wait a
minute what happened to uh uh Cain
disinherited right that's right he's not
listed in this isn't it he mention
up and the days of Adam after he had
begotten Seth Seth was 800 years and he
begot Sons and
Daughters all and all the days that Adam
lived were 930 years and he
died uhhuh and Seth liv5 years and begot
Enos and Seth live after he begot Enos
87 years and begot Sons and
Daughters all the days of Seth were 9912
years and he died
and E Enos live 900 years and begot
Canan and Enos Liv after he begot Canan
815 years and beg got Sons and
Daughters all the days of Enoch Enos
were 95 days and he
died and Canaan lived seven 70 years and
begot
Mahal and Canan Liv after he got Mahal
leel 840 years and beg got sons and
daughters and all the days of Canaan
were 9 10 years and he died and Mahal
Liv 65 years and beg got Jerry and Mahal
leel live after he begot Jared 830 years
and begot sons and daughters and all the
days of Mahal were
895 years and he
died and Jared live 16 and2 years and he
begot Eno Enoch and Jerry lived after he
begot Enoch 800 years and beg got sons
and daughters
okay so the whole thing is now when uh
uh and and I tell you one other thing we
want to go to now because it's Teddy
here when this when men start to call
upon the name of the Lord let's see four
Genesis 4 Genesis
42526 let's let's look at
it 4:25 and 26 yes sir
okay read it then and Adam knew his wife
again and she bared the son and called
his name Seth but God said she have
appointed me another seed instead of
Abel who came
slew and to se and him also was there
born a son and he called his name Enos
then began men to call upon the name of
the Lord see now before that Cain Cain
and his seed did not come call upon the
name of the Lord they did not serve the
Lord the Lord therefore they couldn't be
led by the Lord now somebody go real
quickly and we going to read where it
says long as you led by the spirit of
God you're the sons of God
8 Romans
84 Romans
814 I got all this down but for time
sake you know I didn't go through it but
Romans
8:14 for as many as are led by the
spirit of God
they are the sons of
God so as long as you led by the spirit
of God you are the sons of God that's
why when line when Jesus lineage he
named all of these people and they went
all the way back to Adam which was the
son of God right and when Adam and and
Cain and his daughters did not serve uh
call upon the name of the Lord they
didn't serve God they didn't walk in the
ways of
God and they was around before set
and when sath and his children came they
started to call upon the name of the
Lord therefore they was led by the L the
word of God that's why when when the
Lord looked up on these he said he uh uh
uh uh he said something here nobody pays
attention to I'm putting a little time
in this because I didn't hear this
conversation come up too many times and
when he come up inside the Israel of God
it's time for it to be dealt with yes
sir now let's go to Genesis 6 can start
reading at verse one yes
sir is it Genesis
[Music]
uhhuh start at verse
one and it came to pass when men began
to multiply on the face of the Earth and
daughters were born unto them that the
sons of God saw the daughters of men
that they were fair and they took them
wise of all which they choose and the
Lord said
hold on didn't we read in the New
Testament that the Angels don't give in
marriage or Tak in marriage that is
right that's right but these took them
wives didn't they now look what it look
what it said read the next
verse and the Lord said my spirit shall
not always strive with man for they for
that he also is flesh yet his days
should be 12 years see that he said my
spirit not going always strive with man
cuz he know that the girls are going to
change his
mind change the mind of them therefore
he started to cut the uh uh cut the uh
uh children down cut their LIF span down
but we going to look at this verse here
read that full verse and we going
analyze it here now there were giants in
the earth in those days and also after
that wait a minute so they was giants in
those days right right right did you see
any were they did the Giants come out of
uh uh uh any particular lineage of of uh
men and women coming together sons of
g no it was Giants they said the reason
you had Giants because the Angels left
with the women look then then Goliath
them on the other side of the flood was
giant wasn't that correct
right go ahead and
read and there were giants in the earth
in those days and also after that when
the Sun sons of God came in unto the
daughters of men and they bear children
to them the same became Mighty Men which
were of old men of R now now I want to
put one more thing and we're going to
leave it alone let's go into Genesis the
first
chapter and let's start reading at the
uh uh let uh start reading at verse 11
and God said let the Earth bring forth
grass the herb yielding seed and the
fruit trees yielding fruit after his
kind who
see he said after this kind didn't he go
ahead and read after this
kind who seed is in itself upon the
Earth and it was so and the Earth
brought forth grass and herbs Ying seed
after his
kind and the tree Ying fruit uh fruit
whose seed was in itself as his kind and
God saw that it was good in even morning
was the third day going deal with some
animals now SK down to verse 21 and
continue and God created great whales
and every living creature that moveth
which the waters brought forth
abundantly after their
kind uhuh Wing foul after his kind and
God saw that it was
good and God blessed them saying be
fruitful and multiply and fill the
waters and the Sea and let and let fouls
multiply in the
earth and the evening and morning was
the fifth day and God said let the Earth
bring forth living creatures after his
kind cattle and creeping things and
beasts of the earth after his kind and
it was so and God made the Beast of the
earth after his kind and cattle after
their kind and everything that creepeth
upon the Earth after his kind and God
saw that good now the reason I went here
is because the word after is kind so
whatever your father is that's what you
are Y and if your father can't die you
can't die Angels can't the same Gabriel
that spoke to Daniel went down there and
told Mary that she was going to have
Jesus why is the angel that that last
that long because they can't die then
the Lord made the Lake of Fire for Satan
and his angels why because they can't
die so if the Angels had children by
women then the children should be here
because they could not die
every yall
understand it's all that simple angel
don't give it marriage Lord that's what
Jesus said now you calling Jesus a
lie that's all I have to say
so the sons of God were the one that
walked in the word of God like Paul told
you as long as you led by the word of
God you are my son and what did God said
when he saw these boys mared Cain's
daughter he said my spirit shall not
always strive or shall not always be
walk or shall not always be with man
y'all understand yes
sir that's very clear to me very clear
too
ch right thank you for that add on we
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one moving on to the
next one commissioner Paula a Stanford
asks in first John 1 verse n if we
confess our sins he is faithful and just
to forgive us our sins and to cleanse us
from all
unrighteousness does that pertain to all
confessed sin
all right brother Julius what you got to
say about these sins and confess sins
well it means exactly what it says read
it tzel first 1 John 1 and9 read it it
means exactly what it says go ahead if
we confess our sins he is faithful and
just to forgive us our sins and to
cleanse us from all unrighteousness
let's go to Ezekiel the 18th chapter
real quick and give you an example
another example Ezekiel 18 chapter we
going to read verses 27 and
28 Ezekiel 18 yes sir the Lord means
what he said because he don't want
nobody to be lost that's why you have to
repent Ezekiel 18:27 and 28 go ahead my
brother again when the Wicked Man turth
away from his wickedness that he have
committed and doeth that which is lawful
and right he shall save a soul alive
uhhuh because he consider because he
considered
uhhuh and turn away from all his
transgression that he rep he repented go
ahead he acknowledges transgression so
he turned away from it and go ahead and
he shall surely live he shall not die so
the Lord mean what he say if we confess
our sins he is just and faithful to
forgive us of our sins you have to
acknowledge your transgression and go
and sin no
more that's all I got
ain't no saying a big he said if you
break one you break them all yes sir
that's right James
2 y that is correct all right thank
you let the spirit of God Lead You In
Truth and
righteousness all right we go go to our
next question next question TX Domino
says in Matthew 27: 52 and 53 when the
saints came out of the Graves and went
into the cities what happened to them is
there a place where they await the
return of Jesus or did they die again
Matthew
27 verse 52 and 53 read that tzel and we
will gu caller will let them know what
happened to the ones that came out of
the Grave during that
time and the graves were open and many
bodies of the saint which slept a Roose
and came out of the graves after his
resurrection and went into the holy city
and appeared unto
many now that's what happened what
happened to them they died in they weren
the first that was Ro risen from the
dead uh uh uh uh Elijah raised the boy
from the dead Elisha raised from raised
somebody from the dead Jesus raised some
dead the apostles raised
dead Jesus raised Lazarus from the dead
what happened was they all died
again if that wasn't the case
then what we going to read is wrong
let's go to Colossians the 7 the uh uh
Colossians the uh uh 1 chapter and read
verse 17 and 18
Colossians
chapter and read
18 know why colia is running from
me Colossians 11:7 and
18ans 117
okay and he is the head of the body the
church who is the beginning the
firstborn from the dead that in all
things he might have the
preeminence for it pleased the
father what verse is now 18 yeah that
was
18 read it and he is the head of the
body the church who is the beginning the
firstborn from the dead that in all
things he might have the
preeminence now could he be the first
Dawn from the dead if these people that
was raised or these Saint was still
living right he he was the first born
from the dead that did not die again now
let's go into First Corinthians 15 and
read verses 21 and
22 1 Corinthians 15 21 and 22
uh for Since By Man Came Death by man
came also the resurrection of the Dead
for as in Adam all died even so in
Christ shall all be made
alive goad but every man in his own
order Christ the first fruits afterward
they that are Christ at his
coming so when the dead you going be
made alive at the coming of Jesus right
right then said Christ the first fruit
so now if these people live were still
living he wouldn't be the first fruit
wouldn't it no right but I just put one
little piece on it to put some icing on
it go to First Timothy 6 and read 13-
16 this will be the last of it you said
first
Timothy uhhuh First Timothy chapter 6
verse 13-
16 1 Timothy chapter 6 verse
13 I give thee
charge okay I give the charge in the
sight of God who Quicken all things and
before Christ Jesus who before Pontius
pilot witness a good
confession that thou keep this
commandment without spot unrebuked until
the appearing of our Lord Jesus
Christ which in his time he shall show
who is the blessed and only Pent the
king of kings and Lord of lords who only
have immortality dwelling in the light
which no man can approach unto who no
man have seen nor can see to whom be
honor and power Everlasting
amen and it says to whom who only have
eternal life what is only Me by
himself a nobody else right right he's
the he's the only one and have ont then
the rest of them that come out to grieve
is
dead cut and dry that's all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next next
one Natalie Charles ask if one day is as
a thousand years and second Peter 3:8 is
given how does that translate durin the
creation is a day in Genesis referring
to 1,000 years will it stand to reason
that God's creation took 6,000 years and
1,000 years of
rest all right brother 10 go to Second
Peter 3 read that verse 8 and then the
guest caller share some life from there
but beloved be not ignorant of this one
thing that one day is with the Lord as a
thousand years and as a thousand years
as one
day okay you said second what question
was that now who answered
it that the question is
right um yeah the
question
five okay
if a day is as a thousand years and a
thousand years is one
day okay well you said thousand years
that so you read that in second in
second Peter right right yeah let's go
and what was the rest of that
question so they want to know is a day
in Genesis referring to 1,000 years will
it stand to reason that God creation
took 6,000 years and 1,000 years of
rest well let's examine
it let's go into Genesis the 2
chapter read verses 16 and
17 this is when the Lord told uh uh told
Adam uh not to eat of the tree of the
knowledge of Good and Evil if he did
what's going to happen to
him read it when you get there and the
the Lord God commanded the man saying of
every tree of the garden thou mayest
freely eat but of the tree of the
knowledge of Good and Evil Thou shalt
not eat of it for in the day that thou
eatest thereof thou shallal surely
die okay well we know that man ate of it
didn't y he said in the day that you eat
of it you shall Sur have die that day
didn't he say that
right a lot of ministers start run
around talk about he died spiritually no
no God told him that look uh uh you
going to return to the ground for out
was you out of it you was taken so it's
talking about a physical death is't that
correct
yes now let's go into Genesis the 5th
chapter and read from 1 to
five Genesis 5
1-5 this is the book of the generation
of Adam in the day that God created man
in the likeness of God made it he him
male and female created he them and
blessed them and called their name Adam
in the day when they were created and
Adam lived 130 years and beg got a son
in his own likeness after his image and
called his name
Seth and the days of Adam after he had
begotten Seth were 800 years and he
begot sons and daughters and all the
days that Adam lived were 930 years and
and he
died well then Adam died now the Lord
can't lie a't that's ain't that ain't
that the truth that's the
truth the day you eat that tree you
going to die so Adam live 900 how many
years 930 years that's long than a
24hour day Ain it
yep D the oldest man that ever live was
be how long he live 969
okay should have any man
ever live a thousand years
no because that thousand years that the
Lord is talking about is the Lord's year
uh uh one year is a thousand years now
let's go into Psalms 90 and read verse
one and Skip down to verse four Psalms
90 verse one and Skip down to verse four
Lord thou has been our Dwelling Place in
all
generations for th000 years in thy sight
but as yesterday when it is passed and
as a watch in the
night so all this is told about a
thousand years God gave man 6,000 and
7,000 years and the seventh one is the
day of rest that is the year that's the
time that the Jesus is going to be on
this Earth and it said we going to reign
with Christ for how long Thousand Years
thousand
years and at the end of the seventh day
that the gay man man won't be no more so
that's what it's talking about thousand
years and not a 24hour
day through all the days that he said
and the first day thousand the second th
and the 3,000 and the 4th th000 and the
5th th000 and the seventh one a
thousand that's all I have to
say the S one is all
future all right we hope that answered
your question there as we continue to
move on to our next one next one Harold
Ferguson says I am confused please
explain these two passages to me first
Peter 3 vers 18- 22 in 1 Peter
4: 5 and 6 who is this talking about if
the dead know nothing and cannot hear
also evil angels have already been
condemned to the Lake of
Fire let's go read
it 1 Peter 3rd Chapter Verse 18 through
22 but Christ also have one suffer for
sins the just for the unjust that he
might bring us to God being put to death
in the flesh but quickened by the Spirit
by which also he went and preached into
the spirits in prison which sometimes
were disobedient when when Once the long
suffering of God waited in the days of
Noah while the ark Was preparing werein
few that is eight Souls were saved by
water
she said to 22 so okay the like figure
wherein to even baptism doth also now
save
us I'm sorry go ahead go ahead not the
putting in the way of the filth of the
flesh but the answer of good s good
conscience towards God by the
resurrection of Jesus Christ who has
gone into heaven and is on the right
hand of God angels and authorities and
Powers being made subject unto
him okay uh
um Harold sorry he said so now um this
this passage you got two different
situations going on you know one in
Noah's time and the time when Jesus came
in the flesh they they two different
times so when you read this verse where
it said he preached unto the
spirits uh it's telling you this
happened during the during the days of
Noah
when he was building the
ark okay that's what he talking about
and these Spirits are are angels that he
was talking to or preaching to in the
days of Noah okay so uh and when it
talks about chains where he says uh in
prison them chains of darkness in other
words the Lord fixed it so they can't
uh appear before you like they really
look right they can't show themselves he
took that away from them right so he
that's the chains that the end that's
the prison that the end it called chains
of darkness in the uh uh I think it's
the uh verse four and five chapter 2
verse 4 and five I
think let's go to that second Peter
chapter
2 second Peter chapter 2 okay yeah and
read verse four and
five for if God Spar not the angels that
sin but cast them down to Hell and
deliver them in Chains of Darkness to be
reserved into
judgment and spare not the old world but
save Noah the eight person a preacher of
righteousness bringing in the flood upon
the world of the
ungodly so now that those spirits that
he preached were actually angels in the
days of Noah okay right now uh uh you
also ask about the fourth
chapter of First
Peter so let's read verse
five first Peter 4 and five
yeah who shall give account to him that
is ready to judge the quick and the dead
uhhuh and the there in that verse is
actually talking about um the ones who
were alive and then they physically die
you know like the ones we put in the in
the grave when we bury them they dead
that's the death is talking about in
that in that verse okay when you say the
uh the quick and the dead all right now
read verse uh the quick is the living
like we living right now all right and
the dead is the one we put in the grave
all right now read verse uh six
for for this cause was the Gospel
preached also to them that are dead that
they might be judged according to men in
the flesh but live according to God in
the
spirit now you can't you can't you can't
preach to somebody that's dead and in
the
grave they have no more portion or
anything on this Earth they thoughts all
of that perish okay so this six verse is
talking about a spiritual Dead all right
so now let's go to some verses to
establish what that spiritual dead I'm
talking about go to Luke chapter 9 and
read verse 59 and
60 when you get it go ahead and read and
he said unto another follow me but he
said Lord suffer me first to go and bury
my father but Jesus said unto him let
the bury their dead but go thou and
preach the kingdom of God all right so
he said let the dead bury their dead in
other words you spiritually dead let
them go bury the physical dead okay
that's the that's the dead he talking
about in that six verse of your question
all right one more place in Hosea 13 and
read verse one and
two that'll be
it hoseah 133
and one and two yeah when ephra spake
trembling he exalted himself in Israel
but when he offended in bael he died
uhuh when he start dealing with paganism
and other God serving other God he died
spiritually all right go ahead and read
two and now they sin more and more if
they physically dead how they going to S
more and more right CU they ain't
physically dead they spiritually dead
right even though we call them The
Walking Dead all right that's all I got
on that's
it all right thank you for that as we
move on to our next question yes moving
on uh Anthony horsey asked for you to
share some light on Exodus 21 vers 20
and
21 uh he says I had a brother come at me
with this saying how is this right that
is okay to beat your slaves as long as
you don't kill them this brother is
always trying to cross me up usually I
can handle him but the scriptures I need
some
consel let's go to that Exodus
21 when you get there read that 20 and
21 and then the guest caller share some
light about this slave getting beat at
his servant go ahead brother and if a
man Smite his servant or his maid with a
rod and he die under his hand he shall
be surely punished but not withstanding
if you continue a day or two you should
not be punished for he is his
money okay the answer I want to give you
that you he tell his cat to wait this
brother till he wait till he get him a
slave so when he start having slave
slave then come back and we'll address
this
question but if you don't have no slave
then it's a moot point while we're gonna
talk about
it that's all I have to say all right we
gonna move on to our next question yes
next question and the time is
8817 Fitness Guru have two questions
one does the tribulation happen
immediately after the abomination of
desolation and two when is the second
Resurrection all right brother Julius
share some light on these two questions
all right let's go to Matthew the 24th
chapter and let's look look at the order
of
this Matthew 24 brother tenzel and we're
gonna read verse
15 this is a prophecy and this is what
we are waiting on when this man of sin
enter into this Temple that's going to
be built over in the
land eventually the pope GNA end up
being there go ahead and read at verse
15 when you therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the Prophet stand in the Holy
Place whoo reth let him understand all
right skip down to verse 20 and 21 go
ahead well skip down to verse 21 and get
right to it go ahead for then shall be
Great Tribulation such as was not since
the beginning of the world to this time
no nor ever shall be so this Great
Tribulation is going to be initiated by
the man of sin he is the one that's
going to launch it and start it uh three
and a half years of turmoil and Trouble
on this earth like it never have been
nor ever shall be again so the man of
sin has to get in the Holy place in the
temple and then he's going to launch the
Great Tribulation
now your second question when is the
second
Resurrection yes let's go to Revelation
the 20th
chapter Revelation chapter 20 brother
tenzel and we gonna pick this up and
read verse
11-13 when when the Lord come he going
to put Satan away going to be a thousand
years
now immediately
after let's look at at vers 11 and go
ahead and I saw a great white throne and
him that sat on it from whose face the
earth and the heaven fled away and there
was found no place for them and I saw
the dead small and great stand before
God and the books were open and another
book was open which is The Book of Life
and the dead were judge out of those
things which was written in the books
according to their
works one more and the SE gave up the
dead which were in it and death and Hell
delivered up the dead which were in them
and they were judged every man according
to their works so this is the second
Resurrection which is also called the
Great White Throne judgments that's all
I
got well you could have back up and read
you could have backed up and read where
he said they reign with Christ a
thousand years yeah and the rest of the
de live not until a thousand year were
over with back that up to Let's uh verse
four at
four Revelation 20 and4 when you get it
Tel go ahead and I saw Thrones and they
that set upon them and judgment was
given unto them and I saw the souls of
them that were beheaded for the witness
of Jesus uhhuh and for the word of God
and which had not worshiped the Beast
neither his image neither had received
his Mark upon their forehead or in their
hands and they lived and reign with
Christ a thousand years go ahead but the
rest of the Dead live not again until
the thousand years were finished this is
the first
resurrection so now after the Thousand
Years skip down to verse seven and go
ahead and when the thousand years were
expired Satan shall be loose out of his
prison they go
ahead and shall go out to deceive the
Nations which are in the four quarters
of the earth God and may God to gather
them together to battle the number of
whom is as as the sand of the sea now
verse 10 go ahead and the devil that
deceiveth them was cast into the lake of
fire and brimstone where the Beast and
the false prophet are and shall be
tormented day and night
forever and I saw a great white throne
and him that sat on it from whose face
the who face the earth and the heavens
fled away and there was found no place
for them so now you can read the rest of
it this is the great white Throne
judgment this is the second Resurrection
after uh the Thousand
Years thank you guest
caller all right thank you for that hope
that answered that question let's move
on to our next one next one Malicia Cur
asks do do the PE does the people that
die in the flood during Noah's Noah day
have to stand to be judged or were they
just
destroyed and can you also explain First
Timothy 5 verse 8 what is an
Infidel all right so the people that
died during Noah's time the book say
everybody got to stand before the
Judgment seat of Christ let's go into um
John the 5th chapter John
5 uh St John 5 yeah here and pick it up
at that verse read 28 and
29 St John
528 and
29 Mar not at this for the hour is
coming in the which all that are in the
grave shall hear his voice and shall
come
forth they that have done good unto the
resurrection of life and they that have
done evil until the resurrection of them
Nation so that applies to everybody even
in Noah's town doing the flood everybody
got to stand before that judgment seat
of Christ turn over to Revelation 20
right quick Revelation 20 we'll read one
verse because we know Noah um everybody
else got drowned so let's see what
happened to those that were under the
water or in the sea who died verse 13
read one
verse the Revelation
20 yep in verse 13 and the Sea gave up
the dead which were in it and death and
Hell delivered up the dead which were in
them and they were judg every man
according to their works so they don't
make that first resurrection they go
come up in the second Resurrection right
here and be judged according to their
Works what was the second question
Deborah uh explain First Timothy 5 verse
8 what is an
Infidel Infidel is a
non-believer or someone that opposes
Christianity or someone that's a atheist
or someone that just don't believe in
God Infidel has a few meanings there but
let's go read that uh that first Timothy
5 and pick it up at verse
eight but if any provide not for his own
and especially for those of his own
house he have denied the faith and is
worse than the Infidel so if anybody
want to provide for their own house or
their own family hey the Lord say you
worse than Infidel you worse than a
non-believer because your actions is not
taking care of Home supposed to be
taking care of home first and then let
things spread abroad let's go Psalm 14
let's show another Infidel what can be
in the Infidel category here Psalm 14
and just read that verse one for
me Psalm
14 verse
one the the fool have said in his heart
there is no God they are corrupt they
have done abominable works and there is
none that doeth good and anybody that
continue to hold on to that attitude
that there is no God you don't want to
serve him you want to walk with him hey
you're an Infidel too so you have to
hope that you don't Harden your heart
and get on board with this word of God
that we preach out of every Wednesday
that's all I got
all right we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one be aler say will the people who
flee to the Wilderness or gather will be
married Matthew 22 verse
11 uh they ask please explain all what
you need to wear to be clothed for the
wedding brother Dre we know what we need
but what you say
well uh will they be married yeah
because couples are going to be
fleeing and they are married couples
that's going to be fleing as well but
let's go to uh Matthew 24 Matthew 24 and
we GNA pick it up at 15 we got a couple
of verses here tanzel so 15 go
ahead Matthew
245 stand holy Place whoo him
understand then which being Judea flee
into the mountain now he said let them
which be in Judea flee into the
mountains but when you see this
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel is not just for them in Judea it
is time to
flee we're talking about fleeing and we
talking about Gathering skip down to
verse 21 go ahead
for then shall be Great Tribulation such
as was not since the beginning of the
world to this time no noever shall be
now that time is going to be Great
Tribulation and if you are not in the
place of safety in the wilderness you
are gonna face some drama now skip down
to verse 29 go
ahead immediately after the tribulation
of those days shall the sun be darkened
and the moon shall not give her light
and the Stars shall fall from Heaven and
the powers of the heaven shall be shaken
mhm and then shall appear the the sign
of the son of man in heaven and then
shall all the tribes of the earth mourn
and they shall see the son of man coming
in the Clouds Of Heaven with power and
great Glory so they gonna see him in
heaven and he they gonna see the sign of
the son of man in heaven but go ahead
verse 31 and he shall send his angels
with a great sound of a trumpet and they
shall gather together his elect from the
Four Winds from one end of the heaven to
the other now this is after the
tribulation so after that three and a
half years he is going to gather those
right he's at the Great Sound of the
trumpet he's gonna gather but the other
ones are going to flee and during the
Thousand-Year Millennial period you will
have Mortals and Immortals and yes they
will be
marriage for those that are Flesh and
Blood people but uh Jerome did an
excellent lesson on Friday night prayer
couple of weeks ago called flee to the
Wilderness don't get caught in the Great
Tribulation I would say watch that now
the second question speaks of re uh
Matthew 22 and11 let's go there Matthew
and11 read that when you get it t
and when the king came in to see the
guest he saw there was a man which had
not on a wedding
garment now you ask the question what
should you be clothed with now let's go
to Ephesians now the sixth chapter let's
see what your clothing should be so you
don't come to this wedding Feast not
clothed properly Ephesians 6 pick it up
at verse 13 go ahead when you get it
brother wherefore take unto you the
whole armor of God that you may be able
to withstand in the evil day and have
done all to
stand stand therefore having your loins
GED about with truth and having on the
breastplate of
righteousness and your feet shy with the
preparation of the gospel of
peace above all taking the shield of
Faith wherewith you should be able to
stand able to quench all the fiery Darks
of the
wicked and take the helmet of salvation
and the sword of the spirit which is the
word of God be clothed with the word of
God be clothed with the whole armor of
God that you may be able to withstand
the Ws of the devil that's right that
that helps that's
it all right thank you for that brother
we're going to move on to our next
question with the time check
yes the time is
8:30
MCs in Revelations 22
verse6 does that mean Jesus is the
bright and Morning
Star all right brother
Julius let's go tanzel revelation 22 and
let's read that verse 16 and believe
what it says go
ahead I Jesus have sent my angel to
testify unto you these things in the
churches I am the root and The Offspring
of David and the bright and Morning Star
he says I am the root and The Offspring
so yes he is the bright and Morning Star
let's go to numbers the 24th
chapter let's look at the
prophecy just titles of another titles
for Jesus numbers 24 and read verse 17
when you get it numbers 24 and 17
T num 24 and
17 I shall see him but not now I Shall
Behold Him but not nigh there shall come
a star out of Jacob and a septer shall
rise out of Israel and shall Smite the
corners of Moab and destroy all the
children of shef and Jesus came out of
Jacob son his fourth son
Judah so he is the bright and Morning
Star that's all I
got all right that answers your question
as we move on to our next one next one
brother Jay says in Second Kings 17:
25-33 why
why why did God allow the Assyrians to
serve other gods in the land after
sending Lions and the priests taught the
manner of the land and what is the
manner of the
land all right 2 Kings
17 and they asking for um eight verses
there but you can pick it up at verse 25
and a guest call or take it from
there Second Kings 17 and
25 and so it was at the beginning of
their dwelling there that they feared
not the Lord therefore the Lord sent
Lions among them and slew some of them
but they spake to the king of Assyria
saying the Nations which thou has
removed and plac in the cities of
Samaria know not the manner of the god
of the land therefore he have sent Lions
among them and behold they slay them
because they know not the manner of the
god of the
land and the king of Assyria commanded
saying carry there one of the priests
whom ye brought from then and let them
go and dwell there and let him teach
them the man of the god of the land then
one of the priests whom they had carried
away from Samaria came and dwelt in
Bethel and taught taught them how that
they should fear the lord how be it
every nation made gods of their own and
put them in their houses of the high
places which the Samaritans have made
every nation in their cities wherein
they
dwell and the men of Babylon made sukos
benock and the men of su of of K made
aaral and the men of HTH made asima and
the aites made nebas and tar and tarac
of the seites burnt their children to
fire of adric and vanc the gods of Sean
so they feared the Lord and made unto
themselves the lowest of them Priests of
the high places which sacrifice for them
in the houses of their of the high
places but they fear the lord and serve
their own God after the manner of the
Nations whom They carried out from
then
okay what happened is with them is what
happened with everybody else they had to
be taught and once they going to get
taught then the same thing going to
happen with them like it happened with
everything one else and with Israel
let's go to Deuteronomy the 30th chapter
read verse 15 and Skip down and read
verse
19 what was that Deuteronomy the was it
28th 30 Chapter 30 Deuteronomy
30 read 15 and Skip down and read verse
19 see I have set before thee this day
life in good and death and
evil first 19
verse I call Heaven and Earth to record
this day against you that I have set
before you life and death blessing and
cursing therefore choose life that both
thou and thy seed may
live do now what God did when he sent
that priest down there he taught them
the word of
God taught them about his Commandments
and everything else so now they knew
what good was as well as evil now he let
them have what he always given man gave
made him a free agent so he told him I
said before you good and evil life and
death choose life and live but before he
taught them they didn't know about good
now let's go into Matthew the 15 chapter
uh uh chapter
15 I'm sorry Matthew Chapter
13 and we're going to read from 34 24 to
30 and we're going to look at this
thing Matthew 132
24-3 the parable right read it another
Parable put he forth unto them saying
the Kingdom of Heaven is likened to a
man which s of good seed in his field
but while man slept his enemies came and
so tears among the wheat went his way
but when the blade was sprung up and
brought forth fruit then appeared the
tears also Al so the Servants of the
household that came and said unto him
sir did not thou sow good seed in the
field from when then have it tears and
he said unto them an enemy have done
this the servant said unto him will thou
then go then that we go and gather them
up but he said nay that's while you
gather up the tears you root up also the
wheat with them but let both grow
together unto the heart
and in the time of the Harvest I will
say to the Reapers gather you together
first the tears bind them in bundles and
burn them but gather the wheat into my
barn now this is the same thing he had a
choice of Good and Evil the the the
wheat was the one that de with the truth
and the tars were the one that that the
uh uh dealt with the with a lie with
wickedness do the Lord said let him grow
together he was separate him at the
Harvest right now and and uh let's go to
one other place Revelation 20 and read
verse
12 and I saw the dead small and great
stand before God and the books were open
and another book was open which is The
Book of Life and the dead were judge out
of those things which were written in
the books according to their works
not them guys that uh uh that was in the
land of Israel that the Assyrians took
there if they have never known what the
truth is then how could God judge them
by their
works right so they had to be taught the
truth and once they taught the truth
then they just like everybody else God
let them grow
together and he will judge them at the
time of parted that's all I have to say
right once you talk the truth you expect
to walk in it
all right I hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one he also asked in Genesis 10
verse 1
and5 why was J fat descendance name
changed to
Gentiles
Jerome oh I actually their name wasn't
changed to Gentiles and Gentiles is is
is actually not a name it's it's a title
that refers to uh the descendants of J
fat okay their names is actually
mentioned in the verse so let's go let's
let's go look at the verses you gave um
Genesis chapter 10 verse
one now these are the generations of the
sons of Noah shim ham and japheth and
unto them were Sons born After the flood
uh uhuh Now read two on down and it'll
give you the
names of the descendants of J fat but
their title is Gentiles okay go ahead
and read the sons of japheth goer and
Mard and Mah and Javan and tubal and
meek and Tyrus one more the sons of goer
asan and RAV and togar okay so now take
verse two for example J van we know are
the
Greeks okay Ash canaz those are the
Germans that's why you got them uh
Jewish people over there they call them
ashkanazi Jews because they was over
there in Germany naming themselves after
the land right but the ashkani people
are Gentiles they
Europeans
okay skip down and read that verse five
that they gave
by these were the ows of the Gentiles
divided in their lands everyone after
his tongue after their families in their
Nations yes so all of these are the
descendants of japet and their title are
Gentiles they're
Europeans that's all I
got all right we'll leave it right there
and move on to our next question moving
on Christy Watson said
says why don't iog have altar calls for
salvation isn't that the main issue
confessing our sins and believing Jesus
died and rose
again brother Dre what you
say well
um alter calls for salvation a altar
call doesn't provide you with salvation
alter calls don't give us
salvation you know our faith in Christ
sacrific and our walk in that Faith
that's what does that it's not just
coming and saying we believe and
confessing what I notice in your
question sister is no action behind it
but let's go to James the second chapter
James 2 James 2 yeah I want we gonna
read verses and Skip read verse
14 James 2 and4 we have to do more than
just confess and say we believe in what
Jesus did it's more it's important that
we walk to Walk not just talk to talk it
starts with our confession it don't end
there go ahead what do it profit my
brother do a man say he have faith and
have not works but can Faith save him so
can your faith save you because you
believe give down to verse 19 read that
thou believest that there is one God
thou doest well for the Devils also
believe and
tremble but without know oh vain man th
faith without works is dead and he
called the man a vain man if he beli
that just having faith without works is
going to save
him we confess our sins we repent that
means we turn away from them we have to
do more than just say we believe right
skip down to verse
uh what what what verse we just read 20
20 that was 20 right read verse 26
for as the body without the spirit is
dead so faith without works is dead
also faith without works is there sister
and in your question you talking about
confessing a altar call for salvation
Salvation comes at the end of our faith
let's go to First Peter the first
chapter first Peter the first
chapter read verse three and we gonna
skip from there
blessed be the God and father of our
Lord Jesus Christ which according to His
abundant Mercy have begot us again unto
a lively Hope by the resurrection of
Jesus Christ from the dead so Jesus
Christ sacrifice begat us to a lively
hope of
salvation but we got to walk in this
word it don't just stop there read verse
five
brother who are kept by the power of God
through faith and to Salvation ready to
be revealed in the last time that's when
your salvation come it's revealed in the
last time but we have to endure until
the end because those that endure until
the end the same shall be saved that's
Jesus
word so the altar call is not
it we have to walk this walk too
right that's all I
got sir can I in something yes sir yes
sir the beginning of
every uh uh uh lesson before we get into
it we do what we read the law read the
law read the
law that is better than the altar call
you know why let's go to Matthew the
19th Chapter and read vers 16 and 17
versus uh Matthew
16-9 16- 17 17 and behold one came and
said unto him good Master what good
things shall I do that I may have
eternal life and he said unto him why
callest me thou good there is none good
but one and that is God but will enter
into life life
eics that's pure and simple isn't
it and we give you the Commandments
before every
class keep
them that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question there
sister Deborah as we take a walk into
new
territory yes in the time is
8:47 we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday
February the 5th
2025 me too for you Jones ask in Daniel
10 verse
13 this is an angel speaking correct and
why or what happened that it took 21
days all right why don't we go and read
that Daniel
10 and let's pick it up first
let's pick it up at five and bring in
the appearance of an Angel because it
took 21 days because one angel came to
deliver the message another Angel held
up that angel from delivering the
message and then the captain one of the
chief princes came to help the angel who
was holding up the angel let him go to
deliver the message but let's read um
verse
five then I lifted up my eyes and looked
and behold a certain man clothed in
linen who loins were dir with fine gold
of you fast and his body also was like
the burel of his face as the appearance
of light lightning and his eyes as lamps
of fire and his arms and his feet like
in color to polish brass and the voice
of his words was like the voice of a
multitude so he was coming to deliver a
message even to Daniel and let's skip
down to verse 12 and let's see what
happened what did this Angel say here
then say he unto me fear not Daniel for
from the first day that thou did set thy
heart to understand and to chasten
thyself before thy God thy words were
heard and I am come for thy words so
when Daniel first asks to seek to be
explain his vision he say from day one
hey your word Was Heard and I was on my
way but I didn't get there because the
13 go ahead but the prince of the
kingdom of Persia
with stod me one in 20 days below
Michael one of the chief Prince came to
help me and I remained there with the
kings of Persia so one of the Angels
Satan kept him tied up for 21 days to
not be able to deliver the message to
Daniel but we see here that Michael one
of the chief princes came and got Satan
up off of Gabriel to deliver the message
and verse 14
now I am come to make thee understand
what shall befall thy people in the
latter days for yet the vision is for
many days so he was held up from 21 days
from delivering the message one Angel
was held up by another one until Michael
the chief princes of the Angels Came and
freed him that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question moving on to our next question
sister Deborah's time is a ticket yes
Mark Ash says is it okay for Paul to
give his opinion as law like in 1
Corinthians 7 vers 6 12 25 and also 2
Corinthians 11 verse1 17 because I have
trouble with several writings of Paul it
wouldn't be the first brother Julius
helped him out with those verses it is
quite okay
uh let's go to the scriptures first of
all first of all let's go to Galatians
the 1 chapter
10z people don't people forget Paul was
a
Pharisee well taught in the
law and Paul is not going to say
anything that's contrary and these are
uh Paul was the Apostle to the Gentiles
and these are Epistles to the Church of
Corinth Galatians
1 and read verse 11 and 12 T when you
get it Galatians
1 11 and
12 but I certify you Brethren that the
gospel which was preached to me is not
after man uhhuh I neither receive it of
man neither was I taught it but by the
revelation of Jesus Christ so Paul was
taught by Jesus you know go ahead skip
down to verse skip down to 15 and 16 go
ahead
but when it pleased God who
separate me from my mother's womb and
called me by his grace to reveal his son
in me that I might preach him among the
Heathen immediately I conferred not with
flesh and blood he is another word for
Nations because Paul was the Apostle to
the Gentiles right he was chosen by God
to do that now let's go to their
scripture 1 Corinthians 7 we're not
going to read all but we going read of
it to let you know the thing that PA
said look how PA started this go
ahead firstan 7 and6 7 and6 but I speak
this by permission and not of
commandment he said but I'm speaking by
permission and not a commandment but of
speaking by permission go ahead for I
would that all men were even as I myself
but every man have his proper gift of
God one after this manner and another
after that Paul was a self-made unit to
the Lord he said I wish everybody would
was like me they had the Zeal that I
have but he said hey but the lord gave
every man according to he to his will so
this is what people don't understand
about Paul's writing skip down to verse
12 quickly and go ahead but to the rest
speak I not the Lord uhuh any brother
have a wife that believeth not and she
be pleased to dwell with him that him
not put her away and Paul can say and
Paul can be Paul is right about that
nothing wrong with what Paul is saying
so you could read the rest of the
scriptures on your own but I want to go
to uhh uh second Peter second Peter the
thir
chapter it is not the the if you have uh
any misunderstanding about Paul's
writings let's look at what
Peter second Peter 3 and read verse 16
second Peter 3 and
16 as also in all his Epistles speaking
in them of these things in which are
some things hard to be
understood which they that are unlearned
and unstable rest as they do also the
other scriptures unto their own
destruction and this is the problem a
lot of people read Paul's writing and
they twist the scriptures Paul cannot go
outside of the scriptures sisters and
brothers he cannot go outside of the
scriptures you know so uh this is why we
understand what Paul is saying because
we understood what Peter said but you
got to rightly divide the words and
truth you got to understand it so so you
it has to be an understanding on your
part about Paul's
writings anybody else want to answer
that I think that's it brother I think
you're somewhere where you where it's
unlearned in the scripture are being
Twisted you need to find you another
place to be taught the truth and Paul
said in another scripture follow me as I
follow Christ what is that Dre follow me
as I follow Christ that's sir yeah all
right that's all I got hope that answer
your question is we move on to our next
one next one eera says please explain
Genesis 3
verse4 the serpent being cursed as a
Serpent's nature is to move on his belly
and the dust also Genesis
3:15 explain enemity and the bruising of
the head and
heel all right let's go to that first
Genesis 3
and14 with the serpent being cursed as a
Serpent's nature they don't mention
about him crawling around on his belly
but the guest callers going to share
some light there so read that Genesis 3
and14
and the Lord said unto the servant
because thou Hast done this Thou Art
cursed above all cattle and above every
beast of the field upon thy belly shall
thou go and dust shall thou eat all the
days of thy
life that was just a
metaphor because he was talking about no
snake that craws around let's go to 12th
chapter of Revelation and we're going to
look at this C
Revelation
12 because all she did let's see what
let's see what he's called 12 and9
Revelation 12 read verse
n and the Great Serpent was cast out
that old serpent called the devil and
Satan was deceiveth the whole world he
was cast out into the Earth and his
angels were cast out with him now so
that was so so s that that serpent was
Satan the devil it was no snake that CW
around the garden and the reason he he
cast him down from the all that mean is
he took his power away from him so he
could never pop up in front of no other
person like he popped up in front of
Eve the only time that uh the Lord
allowed that is when Jesus came in the
flesh and allowed him to try uh uh Jesus
that was in Luke the 4th chapter other
than that he took the power away from
but now read the next
one uh that is Genesis 3 verse 15
explain imity and the bruising of the
head in
heel and I will
put go
ahead and I will put imity between thee
and the woman and between thy seed and
her seed and it shall bruise thy head
and thou shall bruise this
heal okay let's first let's pick up who
is the woman let's go in the 12th
chapter of Revelation again we're going
to read one and two and we're going to
skip down to five CU we want to see the
woman and her
seat Revelation
12 and there appear a great Wonder in
Heaven A Woman clothes with the sun and
the moon under her feet and upon her
head had a crown of 12
stars and she being with y'all cried
trell and birth and pain to be
delivered now This Woman This Woman This
Woman was Israel if you're going on your
own you can go to Genesis the 37 chapter
and it let you know that the the uh uh
12 Stars the 12 Tri of Israel and the
sun represent Jacob and the moon his
wife and she paying to be delivered and
what do she bring forth skip down to
verse five
and she brought forth a
Manchild who was to rule all nations
with the rod of
iron and her child was caught up under
God and his
throne so the woman was Israel and Jesus
came through Israel that was Jesus and
so uh uh uh he is sitting at the right
hand of the father now as far as in that
is concerned then it tell you that uh uh
uh uh Satan just like all his
servant have en between God because
they're not subject to the law of God
right so anybody that's that's Satan
didn't don't is not subject to the law
of God neither does his service but it's
for his bruising his heel and bruising
his head I can't read nothing specific
on that so I leave it alone all I know
is that Satan is going to be cast into
the liquor by Jesus don't have to
say all right sister Deborah can we have
a Time Check Yes the time is nine
o'clock all right we are ran out of time
but we want to thank everybody who tuned
in with us and if we didn't get to your
question we'll put it in rotation and
sister debah will make sure that we
answer it in the lineup next Wednesday
as we address the questions then but we
like to also say to all of our viewers
and listeners out there that you can
join us for our black
history our black history session will
begin again this Saturday that'll be
February the 8th and it will be on
slavery we'll even talk about the
slavery before the shores of America and
that'll be at 520 West 138th Street in
Riverdale Chicago I mean Riverdale
Illinois
60827 and that will be at 12: noon so
please feel free to join us as we are in
our black history and we have three more
sessions after that but we'll tell you
about that next Wednesday so until we
all come together again be safe be
blessed stay prayerful and may the Lord
have mercy on us our brother tanzel
close us out Our Father which are in
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debt to us and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen amen amen